[
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of Service Strategy?",
    "answer": "To provide a strategy for the service life cycle."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the processes for Service Strategy?",
    "answer": "Financial Management, Service Portfolio Management, Demand Management, Business Management, and Strategy Management."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Service Portfolio Management?",
    "answer": "A method to dynamically and transparently govern resource investment."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the goal of Service Portfolio Management?",
    "answer": "To maximize the value of the business while managing risks and costs."
  },
  {
    "question": "What process does Service Portfolio Management cooperate with for evaluating proposed services?",
    "answer": "It cooperates with Change Management in the Service Transition life cycle."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Financial Management ensure?",
    "answer": "It ensures we track and associate IT investment and spending with the services provided."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the three major activities in Financial Management?",
    "answer": "The 'ABCs' of financial management: Accounting, Budgeting, and Charging."
  },
  {
    "question": "What principles does Accounting in Financial Management apply?",
    "answer": "Accounting applies Cost Accounting principles to IT spending. We do this to answer the question, 'What does it cost to provide each service?'"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is used to show the funding required to support the defined services at a given level of business activity?",
    "answer": "Budgeting ensures that IT Service Management will have adequate funding to deliver promised services."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Demand Management?",
    "answer": "Demand Management helps a business understand and predict customer demand for services."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of Demand Management?",
    "answer": "To understand, anticipate, and influence customer demand for services."
  },
  {
    "question": "Demand Management rationalizes and optimizes the use of what?",
    "answer": "IT Resources."
  },
  {
    "question": "Demand Management bridges the gap between which categories to ensure accurate predictions?",
    "answer": "Service Design, Capacity Management, and Business Management."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Demand Management role is considered to be the owner in the chain of responsibility?",
    "answer": "Business Managers (Business Relationship Managers)."
  },
  {
    "question": "What three main actions involve Demand Management?",
    "answer": "Analyzing current customer usage of IT services, Anticipating future customer demands for IT services, and Influencing consumption as necessary by financial or technical means."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Service Strategy category seeks to form a relationship with customers to understand their needs?",
    "answer": "Business Management."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which life cycle phases do the Financial and Demand Management process belong to?",
    "answer": "Service Strategy."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the most important Key Performance Indicator (KPI) in Business Management?",
    "answer": "Customer Satisfaction."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Service Strategy category seeks to enable strategic asset integration into an organization?",
    "answer": "Strategy Management seeks to integrate IT Service Management within an organization."
  },
  {
    "question": "Strategy Management seeks to answer what questions?",
    "answer": "Who are our customers?, What business outcomes do they need?, How do the services we provide support those outcomes?, How can we position ourselves to be the only logical provider of these services?, What market spaces do we operate in?, Are there ways to expand our current service offerings into new markets?, Are there unmet needs in our current market spaces for which we can develop services?"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for when a Business Relationship Manager analyzes IT service consumption?",
    "answer": "Demand Prognosis."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Pattern of Business Activity (PBA) in Demand Management?",
    "answer": "The PBA is a workload profile of one or more business activities that helps service providers establish usage patterns."
  },
  {
    "question": "The Pattern of Business Activity measures what four aspects of customer service usage?",
    "answer": "Frequency, Volume, Duration, and Location."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term Duration of Usage mean?",
    "answer": "Duration of usage is how long the pattern of business usage lasts."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term Volume of Usage mean?",
    "answer": "Volume of usage is the amount of activity."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term Frequency of Usage mean?",
    "answer": "Frequency of usage is how often the volume of usage occurs."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term Location of Usage mean?",
    "answer": "The location of usage is where the business usage occurred."
  },
  {
    "question": "The PBA also includes a user profile which is a Pattern of Service Usage that is tied to what?",
    "answer": "A type of user."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Demand Control?",
    "answer": "Demand Control is the way providers control IT service consumption."
  },
  {
    "question": "Demand Management is seen with a PBA alongside what Service Strategy category?",
    "answer": "Service Portfolio Management."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ITIL Service categories can Demand Management be found in?",
    "answer": "Service Transition, Service Operation, and Continual Service Improvement."
  },
  {
    "question": "Inaccurate estimates have negative impacts on which categories and processes?",
    "answer": "SLA metrics, KPIs, Customer Satisfaction, Financial Management, Incident management, Business Relationship Management, and Service Strategy."
  }
]
